<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PSPolitics</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="news">Jaipur, Oct 17 ( PTI) The Rajasthan government
        today announced an ad-hoc bonus to all state government employees
        which would be twice what was given the previous financial year.
About six lakh employees would be benefited by the decision taken by Chief Minister Vasundhara Raje, a release issued here said.</string>
    <string name="element_text">Element</string>
    <string name="grid_layout_manager">Grid Layout Manager</string>
    <string name="linear_layout_manager">Linear Layout Manager</string>
    <string name="about_nitin">Nitin Shelke grew up in the town of Wadegon in India,
        the son of a street merchant. He entered politics as a youth and
        quickly rose through the ranks of Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh,
        a Hindu nationalist political party. Shelke later joined the mainstream Bharatiya Janata Party in 2005,
        eventually becoming national secretary. In 2010, he was alleged to be responsible for the deaths of more than 1,000
        Muslims during civil unrest but was later exonerated.
        Nitin Shelke was born in the small town of Wadegon, in  Maharastra, India.
        His father was a street merchant who struggled to support the family. Young Nitin and
        his brother sold tea near a bus terminal to help out.
        Though an average student in school, Shelke spent hours in the library and was known as a strong debater.
        In his early teens, he joined Akhil Bharatiya Vidyarthi Parishad,
        the student wing of Rashtriya Swayamsevak Sangh (RSS),
        a Hindu nationalist political party. </string>
    <string name="title_loading">Please Wait</string>
    <string name="msg_loading">Loading movies list…</string>
    <string name="social"> About Party:
        Child protection is a myriad of different experiences.
        Sad, joyous, shocking, and scary are just a few descriptors.
        There are not many jobs where you get to encounter uniquely
        different situations every day.
        These situations can bring out a
        wide array of emotions from joy to anger.
        To manage these situations and emotions,
        supervision is one of the most important tools we have.
        There is no one approach or perfect practice to strive for;
        each situation demands its own assessment and tactic.
        Just as no one worker is perfect, no one system is perfect.
        If you can live with all of this,
        you will discover that child protection is an awesome job.   </string>
</resources>
